Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Fast Breeder Reactors, 1969-1979, 1981-1982 and undated
  - 7-23, Atomic Industrial Forum Breeder Policy Committee Correspondence and Minutes, 1976-1979, 5 folders (Box 13)
  - 7-24, Atomic Industrial Forum Alternate Cycle Committee Correspondence and Reports, 1977, 5 folders (Box 13)
  - 7-25, Liquid Metal Fast Breeder Reactor Review Steering Committee Reports, 1977 (Box 13)
  - 24-7-30, Miscellaneous Items, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - 24-7-31, The Liquid Metal Fast Breeder Reactor--Options for Deciding Future Pace and Direction, U.S. Comptroller General, 1982, July 12 (Box 13)
  - 24-7-32, Clinch River Breeder Reactor, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
- Environmental Radioactivity, Nuclear Fuel Cycle, Waste Disposal and Proliferation, 1956, 1966-1978, 1980-1982 and undated
  Comprised of reports, speeches, articles, correspondence, booklets, and clippings discussing nuclear energy. Topics include dangers and safety needs when working with radiation, effects on the environment and the public, storage and waste disposal management, health issues, and the safety of nuclear energy as a power source. This series also portrays a concern that civilian nuclear fuel cycles would be used for nuclear weapons proliferation. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 8-4, Comprehensive Management of Radiation Medical Programs, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - 8-6, The Separation of Nuclear Power from Nuclear Proliferation, by Chauncey Starr, 1978, Feb. 27 (Box 13)
  - 8-9, The Storage and Disposal of Nuclear Waste, Atomic Industrial Forum, Inc., 1980, Sept. 5 (Box 13)
  - 8-12, Report to the President from the Interagency Review Group on Nuclear Waste Management and correspondence, 1978 (Box 13)
  - 8-18, Nuclear Power and Plutonium: the Reprocessing Controversy, by Glen A. Graves, 1980, Sept. (Box 13)
  - 8-19, Nuclear Power and Plutonium: The Reprocessing Controversy Figures, by Glen A. Graves, 1980, Sept. (Box 13)
  - 8-26, Committee on Nuclear and Alternative Energy systems Report, 1976 (Box 13)
  - 8-27, Committee on Nuclear and Alternative Energy Systems, 1976 (Box 13)
  - 8-28, Committee on Nuclear and Alternative Energy Systems Correspondence, 1976 (Box 13)
  - 8-44, Radiation Book I, 1966-1970 and undated, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - 8-45, Radiation Book II, 1968-1971 and undated, 1 folder (Box 13)
  - 8-45, Radiation Book II, 1968-1971 and undated, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 8-46, Radiation, Book III, 1972-1978, 1981-1982 and undated, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - 8-47, Nuclear Power Safties and Disposal, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
  - 24-8-52, Miscellaneous Items, 1956, 1976 and undated (Box 14)
- Energy Conservation, 1967, 1969-1979, 1980, 1983-1984 and undated
  Includes reports from the Energy and Environment Systems Division of the Department of Energy by J. G. Ashbury and others. Also contains articles, clippings, speeches, writings, bulletins, pamphlets, and correspondence regarding conservation, waste disposal, and consumer responsibility to energy management. Discusses integrated energy systems, industrial cogeneration, automotive fuel economy, conservation in public buildings, conservation research, and needs of the future. Includes materials from a NewYork energy conservation workshop. Looks at cogenerations based district heating as ademonstrated mechanism for reducing oil and gas use in the heating market, the potentials of solid wastes as a utility fuel, resource recovery, renewable energy, and improved efficiency. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 9-34, Environmental Considerations of Cogeneration Based District Heating, by Elliot P. Levine and Danilo J. Santini, 1980, Nov. 30-Dec. 3 (Box 14)
  - 9-35, Concentrated vs. Distributed Energy: Employment Based Community Level Differences, by L. J. Hoover et al., 1980, Jan. 3-8 (Box 14)
  - 9-51, Energy Conservation Workshop, 1972, Jan. 12, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 9-52, Space Heating With Electricity: The Promise of Peak -Load Pricing, by J. G. Ashbury et al., 1978, Sept. (Box 14)
  - 9-54, Assessment of Electric and Electric-Assisted Technologies in Residential Heating and Cooling Applications, By J. G. Ashbury et al., 1977, Oct. (Box 14)
  - 9-55, Assessment of Energy Storage Technologies and Systems Phase I: Electric Storage Heating, Storage Air Conditioning, and Storage Hot Water Heaters, by J. G. Ashbury et al., 1976, Aug. (Box 14)
  - 9-59, Solar Availability for Winter Space Heating: an Analysis of the Calendar Period, 1953-1975, by J.G. Ashbury et al., 1979, April (Box 14)
  - 9-60, Effects of the Proposed New Source Performance Standards: A Comparative Assessment of the Energy and Economic Impact, by Paul S. Farber and C. David Livengood, 1978, June 25-29 (Box 14)
  - 9-61, A Cost Allocation Model for Assessing the Impact of Energy Storage Technologies Upon Electric Utilities, by R. Giese et al., ca. 1977 (Box 14)
  - 9-63, POWER'S Energy Management Seminar Summary Report, 1974, Feb. (Box 14)
  - 9-65, Lighting and Thermal Operations, Federal Energy Administration, 1974 (Box 14)
  - 9-72, Conservation, Volume I, 1967, 1972-1974, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - 9-73, Conservation, Volume II, 1969, 1970-1978 and undated (Box 14)
  - 9-74, Waste Material, 1969-1975 and undated, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 9-76, Heat Book 2, 1923-1974 (Box 14)
  - 24-9-80, World Resources Institute, 1983 (Box 15)
  - 24-9-81, Assessing the Potential for Fuel Conservation, by Marc H. Ross and Robert H. Williams, 1975, July 1 (Box 15)
  - 24-9-82. Conservation and Renewables, 1975-1976, 1983-1984 and undated (Box 15)
- Fossil Energy, 1971, 1974, 1978-1981
  Contains reports, articles, clippings, case studies, writings, speeches and correspondence pertaining to fossil energy uses. Topics include coal, natural gas, petroleum, hydrogen, and carbon dioxide, impacts on the evironment from using fossil energy sources, and the supply and demand of such resources. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 10-36, First Full Year of Operation of Widows Creek Unit 8 Limestone - scrubber, by J. F. Shiau and James H. Buckner, 1979, March 13-15 (Box 15)
  - 10-37, A Regional Demonstration Program for Maximum Use of High Sulfur Coal and Maintenance of Air Quality Standards, ca. 1971 (Box 15)
  - 10-40, Jason Critique of a Comprehensive Plan for Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment, prepared by US Dept. of Energy, Office of Carbon Dioxide Effects, ca. 1979 (Box 15)
  - 10-41, The Impacts of Increasing Carbon Dioxide: and overview, by George T. Mac Donald, 1978, Sept. (Box 15)
  - 10-42, Climatic Impact of Increasing Atmospheric Carbon Dioxide, by J. Hansen et al., Science 213, 1981, Aug. 28 (Box 15)
  - 10-68, Government Role in an Oil Shale Demonstration Program, draft, by J. A. Blasy, 1974, Feb. 1 (Box 15)
  - 10-69, Synthetic Fuels from Coal, A Report to the AEC Senior Management Committee, Division of Applied Technology, 1974, Feb. 5, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 10-74, Coal Liquefaction, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
  - 10-78, Oil and Natural Gas, A Proposed Program for Reducing Projected Import Requirements with Goals to be Reached by 1985, by James Spear Taylor, 1973, Dec. (Box 15)
  - 10-82, Coal Gasification, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - 10-83, United States, Atomic Energy Commission Energy Program, 1974 (Box 15)
  - 10-84, The Need for Hydrogen as a Fuel in the Future, by H.R. Linden, ca. 1972, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 10-89, Hydrogen System and Miscellaneous Systems, 1972-1975, 1981 (Box 15)
  - 10-94, Strategic Petroleum Reserve, Federal Energy Administration, 1975-1976 and undated, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 10-98, Industrial Coal Utilization Conference, 1980, April 17-18, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 10-99, Liquefied Natural Gas, Substitute Natural Gas, Alaska, Coal and Coal Gasification, 1961, 1965, 1968, 1971-1976, 1978 and undated, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - 10-100, 1977 Approach to Sulfer Oxide Emmision, 1977, Sept. (Box 15)
  - 10-101, Economic Considerations and Operating History of ase-Load LNG Projects, 1977, Dec. (Box 15)
  - 24-10-103, Coal, 1977, 1981 (Box 15)
  - 24-10-105, Gas Supply and Demand-Impact of Technology 1984-2000, by Henry R. Linden, 1984 (Box 15)
  - 24-10-106, Gas Research Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - 24-10-107, Miscellaneous, 1976, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
- Solar Energy, 1961, 1964, 1968, 1970-1980, 1982 and undated
  Contains articles, clippings, congressional reports, speeches, and writings. Also includes reports, pamphlets, and Bruce Anderson's Solar Energy in Building Design manuscript. Covers views and uses of solar energy especially throughout the home, federal government policy, solar utility systems, architecture, prototypes, feasability, and atmospheric and environmental effets. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 11-1. Solar Energy, Book 1, 1961, 1964, 1970-1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - 11-1. Solar Energy, Book 1, 1961, 1964, 1970-1973 and undated, 1 folder (Box 16)
  - 11-2, Solar Energy, Book 2, 1957, 1962, 1968, 1972-1974 and undated, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 11-3, Solar Energy, Book 3, 1974-1980, 1982 and undated, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - 11-4, Solar Energy in Building Design, by Bruce Anderson, 1975, May, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - An Introduction to the Use of Wind, by Douglas R. Coonley, 1975, July (Box 16)
  - 11-13, Reliability, Maintainability and Materials Performance of Solar Demonstration Systems, by Prem S. Chopra, undated (Box 16)
  - 11-31, Solar Energy Program Plan for Heating and Cooling Buildings, by Robert P. McGee et al., a draft, 1974, Feb. (Box 16)
  - 11-39, 3 SPS Effects on the Atmosphere, by D. M. Rote et al., 1979, Dec. (Box 16)
  - 11-40, An Assessment of the Atmospheric Effects of a Satellite Power System, by D. M. Rote et al., 1979, Dec. (Box 16)
  - 11-42, Environmental Effects of Space Systems, by Donald M. Rote, 1979, Sept. (Box 16)
  - 11-43, Workshop on Meteorological Effects of Satellite Power System Rectenna Operation, by J. L. Lee et al., 1979 (Box 16)
  - 24-11-59, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 16)
- Nuclear Power Industry, 1964-1984 and undated
  Includes pamphlets, reports, articles, clippings, speeches, correspondence, newsletters, and statements and testimonies before joint committees. Documents government involvement in the nuclear industry, industry standards and developments, comparisons with electricity and coal fuels, improving efficiency and construction of nuclear plants, and the economic perspectives of benefits and costs of using nuclear power. Roddis collected materials pertaining to use of nuclear power internationally, especially Canada. Also includes information from the Atomic Industrial Forum (AIF) workshop on reactor construction and operation, AIF newsletters and booklets on nuclear safety, managing waste, and radiation, and a copy of President Ford's statement on nuclear energy. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 12-9, Atomic Industrial Forum, 1977, May (Box 16)
  - 12-10, Atomic Industrial Forum, 1977, March (Box 16)
  - 12-15, A New Approach to Reactor Licensing, report by the Ad Hoc Lawyers Group of the Committee on Environmental Law and Technology, 1971, June 18 (Box 16)
  - 12-16, Integrity of Reactor Vessels for Light Water Power Reactors, 1974, Jan. 14 (Box 16)
  - 12-17, N-45 Inservice Inspection, 1969-1971 (Box 16)
  - 12-18, Nuclear Standards, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - 12-26 Magnox and Advanced Gas-cooled Reactors, 1964-1967, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - 12-27 Pressurized Water Reactors and Boiling Water Reactors, Reactor Descriptions, 1969 and undated (Box 16)
  - 12-28 Canadian Reactors. Book 1, 1967-1970, 1 folder (Box 16)
  - 12-28 Canadian Reactors. Book 1, 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-29 Canadian Reactors. Book 2, 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-30 HTGR and Gas FBR, 1965-1973 and undated, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-31 Electric Power for New England, 1975, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-32 Atomic Industrial Forum, 1981, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-33 Atomic Industrial Forum, 1978, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-35, Nuclear Costs and Forecasts Vol. 1, 1970-1974 and undated, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-36 Nuclear Costs and Forecasts Vol. 2, 1974-1975 and undated, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 12-37 Nuclear Costs and Forecasts Vol. 3, 1973-1982, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 12-38 Nuclear Costs and Forecasts Vol. 4, 1977-1981 and undated (Box 18)
  - 12-39 Nuclear Costs and Forecasts Vol. 5, 1978, Sept.-1980, June (Box 18)
  - 12-41 Atomic Industrial Foruml, 1974, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 12-46 Nuclear Power Information, 1978 May (Box 18)
  - 12-47 Economic and Technical Experience of Nuclear Power in the United States, 1982 Sept. (Box 18)
  - 12-49 Nuclear Power Miscellaneous, 1977-1982 (Box 18)
  - 12-64 Statement by President on Nuclear Policy, 1976 (Box 18)
  - 12-65 McCarthy News Release 1976, Oct. 15 (Box 18)
  - 12-66 Nuclear Industy Miscellaneous, 1976-1984 (Box 18)
  - 12-67 INFO, Atomic Industrial Forum's Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - 12-68 NSAC Reports (Box 18)
- Energy Sources, 1971-1981 and undated
  Includes articles, booklets, writings, speeches, reports, and statements before Senate committees. This series focuses on alternative sources of energy including water, fusion, geothermal energy, and satelite power stations, and discusses continued development of current technology such as gas turbines and research and development in atomic, nuclear, and particle physics. There is also a significant emphasis on off-shore pipelining and ships, especially Navy ships. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 13-1 Energy Sources Vol. 1, 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 13-2 Energy Sources Vol. 2, 1975, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 13-7, Bay of Fundy, 1971 (Box 18)
  - 13-23 Energy Sources, 1981 Nov., 1 folder (Box 18)
  - 13-23 Energy Sources, 1981 Nov., 1 folder (Box 19)
  - 13-24, Miscellaneous Energy Sources, 1976-1977 (Box 19)
  - 13-25 The Los Alamos Clinton P. Anderson Meson Physics Laboratory Fifteen Years Later, undated (Box 19)
- Transportation Energy, 1974-1978 and undated
  Consists of articles, reports, booklets, and studies. Topics look at the benefits of electric and battery-powered cars and ways to combat fuel shortages by substituting coal power or battery power in vehicles, discuss air pollution from emissions, and turbine electric cars. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 14-1 Transportation Energy, 1974-1977 (Box 19)
  - 14-9 Methanol From Coal for the Automotive Market, 1974 Feb.1 (Box 19)
  - 14-10 A Technology Assessment of the Teransition to Advanced Automotive Populsion Systems, by Douglas G. Harry, 1975, Jan. (Box 19)
  - 14-16 Commercialization Strategy Report for Electric and Hybrid Vehicles, undated (Box 19)
  - 14-17 Edison Electric Institute's National Energy Transportation Study, 1978, Nov. (Box 19)
- Floating Nuclear Ship Power/Propulsion Plants, 1970-1981
  Consists of articles, reports, and study reports. Discusses ocean thermal energy conversion, the possibility of power plants or power reactors in the ocean, advantages to ocean siting, and power generation from ocean currents. Includes a proposal for a barge-mounted nuclear power plant, reports by architectural and marine companies, and surveillance reports of marine locations for such plants. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 15-1 Marine, 1972-1977 (Box 19)
  - 15-2 Floating Power Plants, 1972-1981 (Box 19)
  - 15-5 Survey of Ships Capable of Supplying Electric Power to the Consolidated Edison System, 1970, Dec (Box 19)
  - 15-15 Hull-Mounted Nuclear Plant Proposal, 1971, Dec., 2 folders (Box 19)
  - 15-17, Barge Type Nuclear Plants, ca. 1972 (Box 19)
  - 15-21, Deep Sea Mooring, Maritime Research Information Service Index Search, 1977, Nov. (Box 19)
  - 15-26, Ocean Thermal Energy Conversion (OTEC) Power Systems, 1978, Nov. (Box 19)
  - 15-27 OTEC Physical and Climatic Environmental Impacts, 1978, Sept. (Box 19)
  - 15-28, Assessment and Control of OTEC Physical Environmental Impacts, 1978, Nov. (Box 19)
  - 15-29, Physical Aspects of OTEC impacts in the Gulf of Mexico, 1978, Nov. (Box 19)
  - 15-32 Commercial Development of OTEC, 1977 July (Box 19)
  - 15-33 Technical and Economic Feasibility of OTEC (Box 19)
  - 15-34 Ocean Thermal Energy, Status and Prospects, 1977, Sept. (Box 19)
  - 15-35 Comments on Selected Issues of the OTEC Program, 1977, Sept. (Box 19)
  - 15-39 Three Point Anchoring in the Deep Ocean, 1975, Feb. (Box 19)
  - 15-41 Selected Issues of the OTEC Program, 1977 (Box 19)
  - 15-42 OTEC Riser Cable: Problems and Costs, 1978 (Box 19)
  - 15-47 Ocean Thermal Program Plan, 1976 (Box 19)
  - 15-49, The Identification and Selection of Riser and Bottom Cable System Designs for OTEC, 1977, April (Box 19)
- Science and Technology Policy, 1931, 1976-1984
  Includes reports, articles, pamphlets, and correspondence concerning various aspects of United States and foreign policies for science and technology. Considers economic factors and especially discusses nuclear technology. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 16-58 Science and Technology Policy, 1931, 1977-1982 (Box 19)
  - 16-59 National Science Foundation News, 1984, Jan. 26 (Box 19)
  - 16-63 Lettter from Carlos E. Kruytbasch, 1983 Nov.20 (Box 19)
  - 16-67 Remarks by the Honorable Henry A. Kissinger, Secretary of State, to the National Meeting on Science, Technology, and Development, 1976 Nov.17 (Box 19)
  - 16-68 Science and Hope, 1976 Oct. 10 (Box 19)
- Oceans and Policy, 1971-1985
  Includes Roddis's notes, correspondence, reports, pamphlets, articles, and maps. Subjects include ocean pollution, off-shore oil drilling and storage, ocean exploration, and clean energy. Correspondents include the U.S. Department of Commerce and the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 17-13 Workshop on National Needs and Priorities for Ocean Pollution Research, Development, and Monitoring, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - 17-15 National Planning Conference on the Commercial Development of the Oceans, 1971-1973 and undated, 1 folder (Box 19)
  - 17-15 National Planning Conference on the Commercial Development of the Oceans, 1971-1973 and undated, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 17-21 Off-shore Drilling, 1971-1985, 2 folders (Box 20)
- Nuclear Power Plant Siting, 1970-1977 (bulk 1974)
  Consists of reports on nuclear energy centers, evaluations of sites for such centers, and correspondence concerning underwater nuclear plants. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 18-10 Evaluations for Nuclear Energy and Environment, 1971 April 7 (Box 20)
  - 18-11 Evaluations for Nuclear Energy Centers, 1974 Jan. (Box 20)
  - 18-12 Evaluations for Nuclear Energy Center, 1974 Jan. 25 (Box 20)
  - 18-13, 18-14, 18-15 Evaluations for Nuclear Energy Center, 1974 (Box 20)
  - 18-16, 18-17, 18-18, 18-19, 18-20, 18-21, 18-22, 18-23 Radiology/Evaluations of Nuclear Centers, 1974 Jan. (Box 20)
  - 18-24 Comments on the American Nuclear Society Banquet, 1974, July 25 (Box 20)
  - 18-33 Underground Nuclear and Pump Storage Sites, 1970-1973 (Box 20)
  - 18-33 Underwater Power Plant Sites, 1970-1973 (Box 20)
  - 18-35 Nuclear Power and the Public analysis of Collected Survey Research, by Barbara D. Melbar et al, 1977, Nov. (Box 20)
- Energy Research and Development Planning, 1978-1983
  Includes booklets, phamphlets, presentation notes, articles, and writings. Discusses energy planning for the future, energy storage, management and contains reviews of energy consumption and energy resources (fusion, solar, and geothermal). This series also contains membership lists, summaries of past meetings, and present and past panels of the Energy Research Advisory Board. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 19-11 Exxon Symposium, 1978, Sept.27 (Box 20)
  - 19-41 Electric Planning, 1979 Feb. (Box 20)
  - 19-42 Electric Capacity Planning, 1979, Mar. (Box 20)
  - 19-44 Review of Energy Resources, 1978, Oct., 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 19-45 Energy Management, 1978 Oct., 3 folders (Box 20)
  - 19-56 Miscellaneous Review Documents, 1978 and undated (Box 20)
  - 19-61 ERAB Reference Book, 1982 June, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 19-62 AIF Strategic Plan, Fiscal Year 1982/1983, 1982 (Box 21)
- International Utilities, 1953-1974
  Includes correspondence, articles, reports, maps, writings, pamphlets, international government documents, photographs, and Roddis's notes on international utility plants. Subjects cover atmospheric pollution, progress with nuclear power, fuel sources, environmental costs and considerations, safety factors, and the uses of electric power, nuclear energy, uranium fuels, and atomic energy. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 20-1 Argentina, 1956 July 18 (Box 21)
  - 20-2 Australia, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
  - 20-7 Australia--Photographs, 1958, Sept. (Box 21)
  - 20-12 Australia--Peaceful Uses of Atomic Energy, 1955-1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-13 Bahrain, 1974 (Box 21)
  - 20-14 Atomic Energy in Belgium, 1957-1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-15 Atomic Energy in South America, 1956 July 18 (Box 21)
  - 20-18, 20-19 Superelectrification of Brazil, 1970 Mar.-1982 May (Box 21)
  - 20-21 Electric Power in Bulgaria, 1966 (Box 21)
  - 20-22.1 Canadien Nuclear Power, 1955 June (Box 21)
  - 20-23 Uranium Fuel Address, 1957 June 26 (Box 21)
  - 20-29 Chile, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-30 Energy in China (Taiwan), 1955-1958 (Box 21)
  - 20-31 Colombia, 1955-1957 (Box 21)
  - 20-32 Czechoslovakia, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-34 Denmark, 1952-1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-35 Dominican Republic, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-36 Ecuador, 1956-1957 (Box 21)
  - 20-37 Euratom (European Atomic Energy Community), 1957-1965 (Box 21)
  - 20-43 Market Potentials of Euratom Countries, 1959 (Box 21)
  - 20-46 Fiji Islands--Maps/Info., 1975 (Box 21)
  - 20-47 Energy/Electricity in France, 1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-48 Electricitie de France, 1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-49 France, 1956-1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-77 Construction Status of Chinon--Photographs, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-78 Germany, 1964-1967 (Box 21)
  - 20-79 Germany--Atmospheric Pollution, 1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-80 Germany, 1955-1970 (Box 21)
  - 20-89 United Kingdom, 1956-1964, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 20-90 Atmospheric Pollution in England, 1964-1970 (Box 21)
  - 20-132 Nuclear Power: United Kingdom, 1957 Apr. (Box 21)
  - 20-134 Geneva, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 20-137 Greece 1955-1972 (Box 21)
  - 20-138 Electric Power for Greece 1967-1972, Apr. 21 (Box 21)
  - 20-139 Indonesia, 1975 (Box 21)
  - 20-145 India and Atomic Power, 1955-1956 (Box 21)
  - 20-147 Israel 1955 (Box 21)
  - 20-148 Italy, 1956-1964 (Box 21)
  - 20-152 International Atomic Energy Agency, 1969 (Box 21)
  - 20-155 Japan: Nuclear Power, 1957-1974, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 20-184, Korea, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 20-185 Mexico, 1956 (Box 22)
  - 20-186 NATO Science Committee,1968 (Box 22)
  - 20-187 The Netherlands, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-188 Supply/Demand of Electric Power in New Zealand, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-189 Norway, 1956-1960 (Box 22)
  - 20-190 OEEC, 1957-1958 (Box 22)
  - 20-192 Information Conference on Nuclear Energy for Management, 1956-1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-193 Directory of International Organizations in the Field of Nuclear Energy, 1958 Aug.15 (Box 22)
  - 20-194 Pakistan, 1955-1958 (Box 22)
  - 20-195 Panama, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-196 Peru 1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-197 Report on Nuclear Power Program, 1970 (Box 22)
  - 20-198 Phillipines, 1958 (Box 22)
  - 20-203 Portugal, 1953 (Box 22)
  - 20-204 South Africa, 1955 July 11 (Box 22)
  - 20-205 Spain, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-206 Sweden, 1954-1968 (Box 22)
  - 20-210 Switzerland, 1954-1967 (Box 22)
  - 20-215 Thailand, 1956-1957 (Box 22)
  - 20-216 Trip Reports, 1964 (Box 22)
  - 20-217 Turkey, 1956-1958 (Box 22)
  - 20-218 Uraguay, 1956 and undated (Box 22)
  - 20-219 Venezuela, 1956 (Box 22)
  - 20-220 Yugoslavia 1955-1958 (Box 22)
  - 20-221 Russian Power Progress, 1960 Sept. 26 (1 folder) (Box 22)
  - 20-223 Evaluation of the Russian Threat in the Field of Electric Power, 1957 Oct.22 (Box 22)